100% Certified Authentic

Contact Us

Search: [](https://www.bobswatches.com/cart)[](https://www.bobswatches.com/verify_login?account_login=1) Open Menu

Close Menu

* Rolex
    * Rolex Prices
* OMEGA
* Brands

* * *

* * *

* Featured Collections
* Men's Watches
* Womens's Watches

* * *

* Resources
* Rolex 101
* (800) 494-3708 [(800) 494-3708](tel:8004943708)

Search:   

**Privacy Policy**
==================

Last modified: Effective July 13, 2021

In order to register a privacy complaint with Bob's Watches, please do so by sending an email by clicking [HERE](mailto:bobswatches@bearflagservices.zohodesk.com).

Introduction-Who we Are

Our company is CME International, LLC dba "Bob's Watches" ("Company" or "We"). Our primary business address is: 1900 Quail Street Newport Beach, California. We are a United States based entity.

At Bob's Watches, we respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.

This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website [www.bobswatches.com](https://www.bobswatches.com/) or our Bob's Watches Mobile Application (the website and mobile application are referred to for ease of reference as our "Website") and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information.

This policy applies to information we collect:

* On the Website or Mobile Application.
* In email, text, and other electronic messages between you and this Website.
* When you interact with our advertising and applications on third-party websites and services, if those applications or advertising include links to this policy.
* When you enter our store to transact business.

It does not apply to information collected by:

* Us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Company or any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries); or
* Any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries), including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on the Website.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time (see [Changes to Our Privacy Policy](#a286592)). Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

Children Under the Age of 16

Our Website is not intended for children under 16 years of age. No one under age 16 may provide any personal information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 16. If you are under 16, do not use or provide any information on this Website or through any of its features, register on the Website, make any purchases through the Website or in person, use any of the interactive or public comment features of this Website, or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, email address, or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 16 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 16, please contact us at info@bobswatches.com.

Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including information:

* By which you may be personally identified, such as full name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, home address, birthdate, Driver’s License # and copy thereof any other identifier by which you may be contacted online or offline ("personal information");
* That is about you but individually does not identify you, such as username and password; and/or
* About your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website, and usage details.

We collect this information:

* Directly from you when you provide it to us.
* Automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies.
* From third parties, for example, our business partners.

Information You Provide to Us 

The information we collect on or through our Website may include:

* Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our Mobile Application or Website, making a business transaction with us online or offline in person, or requesting further services from us. We may also ask you for information when you enter a contest or promotion sponsored by us, and when you report a problem with our Website.
* Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us.
* Your responses to surveys or feedback that we might ask you to complete for research purposes.
* Details of transactions you carry out through our Website and of the fulfillment of your orders. You may be required to provide financial information before placing an order through our Website.
* Your search queries on the Website.
* Any other information that we may request for background checks to ensure your identity and to ensure that no fraudulent activity is engaged in.
* We shall have the right to remarket to you using any email address provided during any of the checkout processes.  

You also may provide information to be published or displayed (hereinafter, "posted") on public areas of the Website, or transmitted to other users of the Website or third parties (collectively, "User Contributions"). Your User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. Although we limit access to certain pages/you may set certain privacy settings for such information by logging into your account profile, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of the Website with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.

Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies 

As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including:

* Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, location data, logs, and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website.
* Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type.

We also may use these technologies to collect information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or other online services (behavioral tracking).  We also may use these technologies to collect information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or other online services (behavioral tracking). [Click here](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/2790761?co=GENIE.Platform%3DiOS&hl=en%20 "Google Support Chrome Stop Tracking in Browser") for information on how you can adjust your Do Not Track on Android/Google Chrome browser and [Click here](https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT212025 "Apple Help") on how you can adjust in-app tracking requests and [Click here](https://support.apple.com/guide/safari/prevent-cross-site-tracking-sfri40732/mac "Apple Safari Prevent Tracking") on how to adjust settings in Safari on your Apple devices such as iPhone and iPad. Please use your browsers’ settings to adjust your preferences. Some features and functions of the Website may not be operational if you choose to disable certain settings.

The information we collect automatically does not include personal information, but we may maintain it or associate it with personal information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:

* Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
* Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests.
* Speed up your searches.
* Recognize you when you return to our Website.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

* Cookies (or browser cookies). A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website.
* Flash Cookies. Certain features of our Website may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from, and on our Website. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies. For information about managing your privacy and security settings for Flash cookies, see [Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information](#a741158).
* Web Beacons. Pages of our the Website and our e-mails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an email and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).

We do not collect personal information automatically, but we may tie this information to personal information about you that we collect from other sources or you provide to us.

Third-Party Use of Cookies

Some content or applications, including advertisements, on the Website are served by third-parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers, and application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our website. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content.

We do not control these third parties' tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly. For information about how you can opt out of receiving targeted advertising from many providers, see [Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information](#a741158).

Purpose for our Collection of Information

We have a legitimate interest to collect the personal information that we collect for our customers, visitors and registered users.

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

* To present our Mobile Application and Website and its contents to you.
* To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us.
* To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
* To provide you with notices about your account, including expiration and renewal notices.
* To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.
* To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide though it.
* To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Website.
* In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
* For any other purpose with your consent.

We may also use your information to contact you about our own and third-parties' goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information in this way, please check the relevant box located on the form on which we collect your data or adjust your user preferences in your account profile. For more information, see [Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information](#a741158).

We may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to display advertisements to our advertisers' target audiences. Even though we do not disclose your personal information for these purposes without your consent, if you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, the advertiser may assume that you meet its target criteria.

Recipients/Third-Parties to Whom We Disclose Your Information

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

* To our subsidiaries and affiliates.
* To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.
* To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of Bob’s Watches' assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by Bob’s Watches about our Website users is among the assets transferred.
* To third parties to market their products or services to you if you have not opted out of these disclosures. We contractually require these third parties to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them. For more information, see [Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information](#a741158).
* To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it. For example, if you give us an email address to use the "email a friend" feature of our Website, we will transmit the contents of that email and your email address to the recipients.
* For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
* With your consent.
* To law enforcement in the event of alleged fraudulent or unlawful activity.

We may also disclose your personal information:

* To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
* To enforce or apply our [Terms of Use](https://www.bobswatches.com/terms-and-conditions "terms of use") or terms of [Seller's Terms and Conditions](https://www.bobswatches.com/shipping-label-terms "Seller's Terms and Conditions") and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.
* If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Bob’s Watches, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

If You Are a European Union Resident:

It is Bob's Watches' intention to comply with the General Data Protection Regulation 2016/679. To that end, we have put in place appropriate safeguards based on the sensitivity of "personal data" as defined in the GDPR to protect personal data that you provide to us if you are an EU resident in the European Union at the time you make a transaction. The following applies to EU residents that transact from the European Union:

* If we collect personal information from EU residents based on requests for service made by such EU residents, then we do intend to transfer your personal data outside of the European Union for purposes of fulfilling your request. Our servers and officer personnel are located in the United States, specifically, in California, USA. 
* We use reasonable measures to ensure that your personal data is kept confidential and only disclosed as set forth in this Privacy Policy.
* We only store your personal data for the period of time as is necessary to utilize the personal data and will delete your personal data after it is no longer necessary to retain once we have fulfilled our services that you have requested.
* Our services do not utilize “automatic decision making” pursuant to the GDPR definition therefore.
* You have the following rights as set forth below to control our use and dissemination of your Personal Data, to achieve any of these rights please send an email with the title, for example: "GDPR Right of Access Request" by clicking [HERE](mailto:bobswatches@bearflagservices.zohodesk.com).
    * Right of Access: Please contact us to register a request for Right of Access request.
    * Right of Correction: Please contact us to update or correct your personal data.
    * Right of Erasure: Please contact us to request erasure of your personal data from our database and servers.
    * Right to Object to Processing: Please contact us to opt out of processing of your personal data.
    * Right of Data Portability: Please contact us to request data portability of your personal data.
    * Right to Withdraw Consent: Please contact us if you would like to request a change to your consent or withdraw your previous consent.
* Please note that your enforcement of any of the above referenced rights may limit or frustrate Bob's Watches ability to provide a requested service to you. Further, at the time your request is made Bob’s Watches may request appropriate verification of your citizenship prior to accomplishing the requested rights.
* Bob's Watches will make commercially reasonable efforts to respond and accomplish the requested rights within the timeframes set forth in the GDPR.

Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

* Tracking Technologies and Advertising. You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe's website. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.
* Disclosure of Your Information for Third-Party Advertising. If you do not want us to share your personal information with unaffiliated or non-agent third parties for promotional purposes, you can opt-out by logging into the Website and adjusting your user preferences in your account profile, checking or unchecking the relevant boxes or by sending us an email with your request to [info@bobswatches.com](mailto:info@bobswatches.com "Third Party Advertising Request").
* Promotional Offers from the Company. If you do not wish to have your contact information used by the Company to promote our own or third parties' products or services, you can opt-out at any other time by clicking 'Unsubscribe' or by sending us an email stating your request to [HERE.](mailto:bobswatches@bearflagservices.zohodesk.com%20%20 "Bear Flag Promotional Offers Support") If we have sent you a promotional email, you may send us a return email asking to be omitted from future email distributions. This opt out does not apply to information provided to the Company as a result of a product purchase, warranty registration, product service experience or other transactions.

We do not control third parties' collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. However these third parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way. You can opt out of receiving targeted ads from members of the Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI") on the NAI's website.

California residents may have additional personal information rights and choices. Please see [Your California Privacy Rights](#a820658) for more information.

Accessing and Correcting Your Information

You can review and change your personal information by logging into the Website and visiting your account profile page.

You may also send us an email at [HERE](mailto:bobswatches@bearflagservices.zohodesk.com%20%20 "Bear Flag Accessing and Correcting Your Info Help") to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

If you delete your User Contributions from the Website, copies of your User Contributions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other Website users. Proper access and use of information provided on the Website, including User Contributions, is governed by our [Terms of Use](https://www.bobswatches.com/terms-and-conditions "Terms and Conditions"). 

California residents may have additional personal information rights and choices. Please see [Your California Privacy Rights](#a820658) for more information.

Your California Privacy Rights

If you are a California resident, California law may provide you with additional rights regarding our use of your personal information. To learn more about your California privacy rights, visit [https://www.bobswatches.com/privacy-policy/ccpa-privacy-notice](https://www.bobswatches.com/privacy-policy/ccpa-privacy-notice).

California's "Shine the Light" law (Civil Code Section § 1798.83) permits users of our App that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email by clicking [HERE](mailto:bobswatches@bearflagservices.zohodesk.com "Bear Flag Email for Your California Privacy Rights").

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. We urge you to be careful about giving out information in public areas of the Website like message boards. The information you share in public areas may be viewed by any user of the Website.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

Changes to Our Privacy Policy

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page with a notice that the privacy policy has been updated on the Website home page. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable email address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes.

Contact Information

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at:

1900 Quail St.  
Newport Beach, CA 92660

or via our toll-free number:

1-800-494-3708

To register a complaint or concern, please contact us at info@bobswatches.com

* Privacy Policy

#### Newport Beach

1900 Quail St. Newport Beach, CA 92660

MON - FRI 9AM - 5PM (PST)

#### Naples

380 10th St. S Naples, FL 34102

MON - FRI 9AM - 5PM (EST)

**Our Company**

**Services & Support**

**Buying & Selling**

**Shipping & Returns**

* * *

### Timeless Style Delivered To Your Inbox

Subscribe today to receive email updates on our timepieces.

    Your email address Subscribe

© 2024 Bob's Watches. All Rights Reserved

[Privacy](https://www.bobswatches.com/privacy-policy) · [Terms](https://www.bobswatches.com/terms-and-conditions) · [Sitemap](https://www.bobswatches.com/site-map) · [Accessibility](https://www.bobswatches.com/accessibility-help)

All rights reserved. Bob's Watches is not affiliated with Rolex S.A., Rolex USA, or any of its subsidiaries.

Bob's Watches is an independent watch dealer and is not sponsored by, associated with and/or affiliated with Rolex S.A., Rolex USA, or any other brand listed on its website. Bob's Watches only sells pre-owned watches and provides its own warranties on the watches it sells. The brand names and associated model names for Rolex, OMEGA and other manufacturers are the trademarks of their respective owners.

Need Help?
----------

* * *

Our team is ready to assist with all of your watch needs.

Chat Now
